https://frenchoil.com/privacy-policy/

PhoneCountry*
Country*AfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCôte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRéunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
Country*
State
State / Province / Region
CountryDepartment You Wish To Contact**Department You Wish To Contact*CompactionComposite PressFiberHuman ResourcesHydraulic PressLamination PressMarketingOilseed Extraction EquipmentParts & ServicePolymer EquipmentRubber MixerRubber Molding PressHow Did You Hear About French?*How Did You Hear About French?*Web SearchMagazineReferralEmail NewsletterSocial MediaOnline DirectoryTradeshowCurrent CustomerOtherMessage*French Newsletter
I would like to opt-in to receive French’s newsletterPrivacy*
By using this form you agree with the storage and handling of your data by this website.EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
xNewsletter Sign-Up
Sign up for our NewsletterWant to stay up to date on French innovations and news?
Opt in to receive periodic e-mails with industry and product news.First Name*Last Name*Email*
Address*
Country *AfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCôte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRéunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
Country
Areas of Interest*Areas of Interest *
Company News
Composite Molding
Hydraulic Press News
Oilseed Processing
Printed Circuit Board Manufacturing
Plastic Card Manufacturing
Rubber Mixing
Rubber and Plastic Molding
Rubber and Plastic Production
Trade Shows and EventsPrivacy*
By using this form you agree with the storage and handling of your data by this website.CAPTCHA
x
Search for:
French Oil Mill Machinery CompanyFamily Owned U. S. Company Since 1900
French Oil Mill Machinery Company and its subsidiaries, including T.H.T. Presses, Inc. (collectively, “French Oil”) respect and value your privacy. This privacy policy (“Policy”) explains how French Oil collects, shares, and uses your personal information, and provides you with information about your rights and how to contact French Oil to exercise those rights.About Us
If you have any questions about this Policy, data protection at French Oil, or to exercise your rights as stated under this Policy, you may contact us.The contact information for French Oil’s corporate headquarters is as follows:
French Oil Mill Machinery Company
1035 West Greene St. P.O. Box 920
Piqua, OH United States 45356-0920
Telephone: 1-937-773-3420
EmailPersonal Information Collected and French Oil’s Purpose
When you visit any French Oil website, French Oil webservers may record technical details that allow you to use, or enhance your use of, the website. French Oil may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about how you use French Oil’s websites. French Oil may collect from you through websites or any communication provided to us by you or any other person representing a company that you are affiliated with, or may obtain from third parties, certain personal information, such as your name, your contact information including your e-mail address and telephone number, or details regarding the company you work for or contact us on behalf of.Purpose of Collecting and Processing Personal Information
French Oil may use your personal information for the purpose of processing any request you may have made, or future requests you may make, in order to enhance your or other users’ experiences when interacting with French Oil, to keep you informed about French Oil products and services, to evaluate and improve French Oil’s marketing activities, and to evaluate and improve French Oil’s business and customer experiences. The processing of your personal information in these contexts qualifies as a legitimate interest under the European Union and European Economic Area’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) and is necessary for French Oil to perform, improve, and market its products and services.Transferring and Sharing of Personal Information
French Oil may use third parties to provide information technology services that may affect your personal information.  French Oil may use web analytics tools offered by third party service providers that may use your personal information to generate detailed statistics about the French Oil websites’ traffic and traffic sources for French Oil’s legitimate use and benefit. French Oil may share your contact details with third parties in order to fulfill a request you have made for products, services, or information, to provide certain business or market analysis services, or to perform direct marketing assistance services to French Oil.French Oil takes appropriate measures to ensure that your personal information is well protected at all times. When French Oil uses third parties to provide services that may affect personal information, French Oil will do so under a data processing agreement that binds service providers to the strict data protection requirements of the GDPR.Moreover, your personal information may be transferred to data processors located in countries outside the European Economic Area, specifically the United States.  The transfer of personal information to the United States will be performed in accordance with the principles set forth in the E.U.-U.S. Privacy Shield.Other than in furtherance of French Oil’s own legitimate uses, French Oil will not share your personal information with third parties unless French Oil has asked and obtained your consent.Retention Period
French Oil will retain your personal data information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined herein or as required by law.Rights as to the Personal Information
As to your personal information, you retain several rights that you may exercise at any time, including:The right to object to the processing of your personal information, which you may exercise by simply contacting us with such request.The right to access your personal information, including access to information about the origin of your personal information and the purpose for its collection.The right to request that the personal information be corrected.The right to request the personal information be blocked, erased, or deleted.The right to demand restrictions on the processing of your personal information.The right to have your personal information transferred to you or to a third party.The right to withdraw your consent at any time, to the extent French Oil’s use and processing of your personal information required your express consent.The right to contact your designated Data Protection Authority with a complaint. A list and contact information for Data Protection Authorities is available by clicking here: http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htmDirect Marketing Opt-Out
If you receive direct marketing communications from French Oil, you may opt-out by sending an email or by clicking on the unsubscribe link that is provided to you in such communication.Your California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding French Oil’s use of your personal information. To learn more about your California privacy rights please visit the Privacy Notice for California Residents.Updates of this Policy
French Oil will review this Policy regularly and update it whenever necessary. French Oil will post such changes on its websites.Date of last update: January 2020
Services and SupportSolutions that Fit Your Exact Needs - Aftermarket Parts, Maintenance, Rebuilds, Retrofits
Learn More
Frenc-RWD-Specs
